<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aavishkar 2018</string>
    <string name="label_create_post_activity">Create post</string>
    <string name="label_post_detail_activity">Post detail</string>
    <string name="label_image_detail_activity">Image</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_profile">Create profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_profile">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_post">Edit post</string>

    <string name="text_take_photo">Take photo</string>
    <string name="text_pick_photo">Pick from Gallery</string>
    <string name="button_title_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_ok">OK</string>

    <string name="hint_title">Title</string>
    <string name="hint_description">Description</string>

    <string name="message_post_was_created">Post was created</string>
    <string name="error_fail_create_post">Fail to create post</string>
    <string name="error_fail_load_image">Fail to load image</string>
    <string name="error_fail_crop_image">Fail to crop image</string>
    <string name="error_smaller_image">Image is too small. Required image size 100x100 px</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_file_type">Incorrect file type</string>
    <string name="error_bigger_file">File size is bigger than 10Mb</string>
    <string name="message_creating_post">Creating post ..</string>
    <string name="message_saving">Saving ..</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_image">Image is required</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_title">Title is required</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_description">Description is required</string>
    <string name="error_post_title_length">Max length of the title should be less than 255 symbols</string>
    <string name="error_fail_remove_post">Fail to remove post</string>
    <string name="message_post_was_removed">Post was removed</string>
    <string name="error_fail_update_post">Fail to update post</string>
    <string name="error_post_was_removed">Post was removed</string>
    <string name="confirm_deletion_post">Delete this post?</string>

    <string name="comment_text_hint">Enter your comment…</string>
    <string name="button_post_comment">Post comment</string>

    <string name="label_comments">Comments (%1$d):</string>

    <string name="create_post_menu_label">Post</string>
    <string name="create_post_full_menu_label">Create post</string>
    <string name="sign_out_menu_label">Sign out</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_menu_label">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="button_title_save">Done</string>
    <string name="button_title_continue">Continue</string>

    <!-- Strings related to registration and login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_name">Name</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="prompt_conf_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="action_create_profile">Continue</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="error_profile_name_length">Max length of the name should be less than 120 symbols</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_confirm_password">Wrong password confirmation</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="permissions_not_granted">Cancelling, required permissions are not granted</string>
    <string name="error_fail_create_profile">Fail to create profile</string>
    <string name="error_fail_update_profile">Fail to update profile</string>
    <string name="text_login">Thank you for using our application! Please, sign in for continue your action.</string>
    <string name="error_authentication">Authentication failed.</string>
    <string name="error_google_play_services">Google Play Services error.</string>
    <string name="button_login_with_facebook">Login with facebook</string>
    <string name="button_login_with_google">Login with google</string>


    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="removing">Removing...</string>
    <string name="error_general">Somthing went wrong.</string>
    <string name="error_general_post">Somthing went wrong with post, id: %1$s</string>
    <string name="internet_connection_failed">No internet connection</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->

    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <string name="profile_menu_item">Profile</string>
    <string name="collapse_text_label">show less</string>
    <string name="expand_text_label">show more</string>
    <string name="add_complain">Complain</string>
    <string name="edit_post_menu">Edit post</string>
    <string name="delete_post_menu">Delete post</string>
    <string name="complain_text">You can complain to this post if it contains violence,
        bullying and threats, hate speech, tragic events and sexually explicit contents.
        Nobody will see the post if you complain to it. You can\'t delete your complain.</string>

    <string name="send_comment_button_label">Send</string>
    <string name="posted_by_label">Posted by:</string>

    <plurals name="posts_counter_format">
        <item quantity="one">post</item>
        <item quantity="other">posts</item>
    </plurals>

    <plurals name="likes_counter_format">
        <item quantity="one">like</item>
        <item quantity="other">likes</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="posts_label">Posts:</string>
    <string name="complain_sent">Complain was sent successfully</string>
    <string name="now_time_range">now</string>

    <string name="duration_minutes_shortest">%1$d m</string>
    <string name="duration_hours_shortest">%1$d h</string>
    <string name="duration_days_shortest">%1$d d</string>
    <string name="duration_week_shortest">%1$d w</string>

    <string name="post_image_transition_name" translatable="false">post_image_transition</string>
    <string name="post_author_image_transition_name" translatable="false">post_author_image_transition_name</string>
    <string name="message_new_post_was_created">New post was created</string>

    <plurals name="new_posts_counter_format">
        <item quantity="one">%1$d new post</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d new posts</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="edit_comment_menu_item">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete_comment_menu_item">Delete</string>
    <string name="message_comment_was_removed">Comment was removed</string>
    <string name="message_comment_was_edited">Comment was edited</string>
    <string name="title_edit_comment">Edit comment</string>

    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">LET'S R</string>

    <!--Firebase errors-->
    <string name="permission_denied_error">Please check your rules to access the Firebase Realtime Database</string>
    <string name="title_activity_exhibition">Exhibition</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!---Viewpager Strings-->
    <string name="title_1">Title1</string>
    <string name="title_2">Title2</string>
    <string name="title_3">Title3</string>
    <string name="title_4">Title4</string>

    <string name="text_1">Vaishali Thakkar is currently associated as a co-organizer with RGSoC and Linux kernel co-coordinator for Outreachy. She is also a freelance kernel hacker, system programmer, foss program manager, and a tech writer and speaker. She was a Google Summer of Code mentor in the year 2016. Vaishali is an avid speaker and has engaged with various tech and open-source conferences which include the FOSSASIA Summit and the Open Source Summit Europe organized by The LINUX Foundation. It is an honour of NIT Durgapur and AAVISHKAR, Vaishali Thakkar has kindly consented to be our guest speaker and engage the students and the institute with her numerous experiences in the world of Open-Source.</string>
    <string name="text_2">Shri Anurag Srivastava is the present District Magistrate of Darjeeling. He has done his B. Tech from IIT Kanpur in the year 2005 and got through civil services. He has served various government sectors as an IAS officer which is the most elite public management cadre of Government of India. It is an honour of NIT Durgapur and AAVISHKAR to host Shri Anurag Srivastava as our guest speaker and engage the students and the institute with his innumerable life experiences.</string>
    <string name="text_3">Listed among the top 50 innovators, skilled in Machine Learning, Image Processing and Pattern Recognition, with 37 research items and 92 citations to this credit, entrepreneur at RootAlpha, chief research officer at Twelit, co-founder and CRO of Roovx, and this may seem to go n since his LinkedIn profile doesnt seem to stop boasting about his achievements and experiences, it is nothing but a matter of pride that a scientist-entrepreneur of his stature will grace our fest, Aavishkar. Mr. Sabyasachi Mukhopadhyay, researcher in the Department of Physical Sciences at IISER Kolkata, has consented to be our guest speaker and we surely await eagerly for him t impart some knowledge and pearls of wisdom. </string>
    <string name="text_4">Dr. Asok Kumar Mallik is currently an Honorary Distinguished Professor at Indian Institute of Engineering Science and Technology, Shibpur. He was a Professor of Mechanical Engineering at the Indian Institute of Technology Kanpur from 1982 to 2009. He was the first occupant of S. Sampath Institute Chair (Professorship) established in 2006. He has been elected as an Institute Fellow at IIT Kanpur.He has taught a large number of UG and PG courses, mainly in the broad area of Mechanics He has fabricated a large number of teaching (visual) aids, two educational movies and a forty-lectures video course for transmission in a national channel. Lately he is involved in a series of popular lectures on Elementary Mathematics.His research areas include Analysis and Control of Mechanical Vibration, Nonlinear Dynamics, Kinematics and Robotics. He has so far guided 9 PhD and 50 M. Tech students. Along with his students and colleagues, he has authored seventy research papers in International Journals. Many results reported by him find prominent mention in a number of international textbooks and handbooks. He has authored/coauthored six textbooks published in India and abroad. A stalwart in Mechanical Engineering and Mathematic,one of the finest professors the country treasures, it is a privilege of NIT Durgapur and AAVISHKAR, Dr. Asok Kumar Mallik has kindly consented to be our guest speaker and engage the students and the institute with his life experiences. </string>
    <string name="text_5">Gyatk, a Kochi-based company engaged in innovations and prototypes of automotive engines, has now developed a fuel hybrid engine. The product was one of just eight innovations amongst 1,000 competitors to win the India Innovation Growth Program (IIGP) Gold Medal from a panel of experts in technology commercialisation appointed by the IC2 Institute of The University of Texas at Austin. Gyatk is one of the IIGPs sponsored by the Department of Science  Technology - Government of India and Lockheed Martin Corporation.The man behind this pathbreaking innovation is none other than Das Ajee Kamath, founder and Chairman of Gyatk who hails from Bhilai, has revolutionised the automobile sector by making internal combustion engine that can run in any fuel from petrol to diesel and even bio fuel. His invention has been granted patents in 51 countries worldwide (including the USA, Japan, China, India and European Union countries), covering all relevant economic zones, and is licensee of intellectual property rights in India. But, Kamath intends to launch his invention in governments ‘Make of India’project.It fill us with immense pride in disclosing the fact and letting all know Ajee Sir is an alumni of our institute :Mechanical Engineering from National Institute of Technology, Durgapur(batch of 1990) and he would be delivering the keynote speech in our first edition of "Aavishkar". We are. more than delighted of his consent to grace our technical fest with his presence and looking forward to listening to his share of experiences and struggles. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_schedule">ScheduleActivity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="arvind">Arvind Satya</string>
    <string name="subham">Shubham Singh</string>
    <string name="vikram">Vikram Reddy</string>
    <string name="adarsh">Adarsh Singh</string>
    <string name="anuj">Anuj Maurya</string>
    <string name="akash">Akash Agarwal</string>
    <string name="punit">Punit Drolia</string>
    <string name="piyush">Piyush Jain</string>
    <string name="shreyashree">Shreyashee Sinha</string>
    <string name="subranshu">Subranshu Mohanty</string>
    <string name="mntc">Maths and Tech Club</string>
    <string name="glug">GNU/Linux Users Group</string>
    <string name="sae">SAE</string>

    <string name="text1">We can be nothing other than thankful and proud for the Armed Forces of our country, cause the Indian Army is what makes our country stand out. This Aavishkar, in collaboration with the Indian Army,  we present an exclusive event wherein Armed vehicles and weaponry will be displayed and demonstrations performed elaborating certain mechanisms and techniques. A huge shout out to all the budding technocrats and autocrats, to cultivate their understanding and knowledge in the field of National Security, we are affirmative of this event's participation footfall and success. See you at the arena!</string>
    <string name="text2">What is the use of a house if you haven’t got a tolerable planet to put it on? A nation that destroys its soils destroys itself. Forests are the lungs of our land, purifying the air and giving fresh strength to our people. It’s high time for the need of technological advancements which can lead us towards a sustainable planet. Prakriti, the official environmental club of NIT Durgapur brings to you EnSignia, a badge of recognition for the greengineers, who work for the betterment of the mother earth.  Sustainability is about ecology, economy and equity. Prakriti invites entries for projects which not only promotes sustainable development but are also equally feasible. Waste not the smallest thing created, for grains of sand make mountains, and atomies infinity. Interested candidates can apply in teams of 4 and fill in their entries in the Google form link mentioned below. Each team has to give an abstract of their project proposal. Based on their abstracts, participating teams will be selected. Each participating team has to come up with a working model (can be software based too). Their projects will be evaluated not only by the judges but by the technical spectators who come to visit their projects on the day of exhibition through online voting portal. Attractive cash money waits for the top 2 teams along with certificates. Also the participating teams can constantly contact Prakriti for guidance and support. Because we believe conservation is a state of harmony between men and land. </string>
    <string name="text3">Aavishkar, the official tech fest of NIT Durgapur, presents the most exciting event of all - the cycle stunt. It involves several dangerous stunts performed by professionals in bicycles. Being such a risky event is what makes it even more exciting. This event will also include several stunts with the help of scooties. Thrill is something that is inculcated in each and every college students mind. This event guarantees thrill and even more. So get ready to witness something as amazing as this in none other place than our college itself. Excited surprises await everyone who comes to witness this wonderful event. </string>
    <string name="text4">‘Entziffern’ is all about breaking the stereotype that caring for environment can’t be fun. There are many innovative and interesting ways to bring to people’s knowledge about how deeply we’ve depleted our environment. The event is a reminder of how unrecognized some species are even though they’re around us every time. The event is also a step towards recognizing the major days and organizations devoted towards working towards the upliftment of the prevalent environmental conditions.</string>
    <string name="text5">Maserati or Mitsubishi?Honda or Toyota? Hold on. Reality Check. Maruti Suzukior Mahindra?Bajaj or Tata Motors?Car brands are always intriguing to humans and definitely NITians. So what could be better than an exhibition of the finest four wheelers and two wheelers in the country,most reliable and popular car brands of the year on display right on the grounds of the technical fest "AAVISHKAR" in the campus of NIT Durgapur. Shout out to all th automobile enthusiasts, let the beauty of such beasts(read:car) marvel you this Aavishkar : presenting AUTO-EXPO. </string>


</resources>
